

JOSE A. MENDEZ

WEB / MOBILE DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

LITEBOX | Frontend Developer

OCT 2021 - JAN 2023

- I collaborated as a frontend developer in the development of the marina administration system for a client in the United States.
- I reduced the bugs found in the frontend by 15%. This generated a 20% increase in the application's performance.
- I worked on the development of new layouts, forms, API consumption, data manipulation on the client, as well as the refactoring of several components, all of this adapted to the requirements requested by the client.

Technologies: React | TypeScript | GIT | Styled Component

DIGIFIANZ | Web Developer

JAN 2018 - SEP 2021

- I was in charge of the development and deployment of at least 20 projects for well-known companies.
- I collaborated with Designers and Project Managers to define new ideas and propose efficient solutions such as: Implementation of Carousels, visual effects, organization of sections, animations, among others.
- I improved the usability, accessibility and performance of the websites under my charge by 70% through the use of Lighthouse, SEO techniques and Pingdom.
- I worked on the development of layouts, forms and modules for the websites

Technologies: HTML | CSS | JavaScript | jQuery | HubSpot | WordPress

PROFILE

I am a developer with experience in web and mobile technologies specialized in providing agile solutions.

I have a great motivation to continue improving my skills and growing professionally, which is why I am always interested in learning, testing and applying new tools or solutions.

If you want to know more about me, I invite you to visit my personal portfolio.

CONTACT



+54 911 55646402



jalejandro.mendezs@gmail.com



alodor.vercel.app



in/alejo-mndz/



CABA - Buenos Aires

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: JavaScript | Python | TypeScript |

HTML | CSS

FRAMEWORKS: React | React Native | Node |
Express | Next | Bootstrap | Material UI

DATABASE: MySQL | PostgreSQL

TOOLS: GIT | Styled Components | Redux | Jest

| Testing Library

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native | English Al

HOBBIES

EDUCATION

Language Market

JAN 2022 - JAN 2023

English Student

Platzi

FEB - DEC 2017

Front-End Arquitect

University José Antonio Anzoátegui

APR 2014

Computer Engineering

Cycling | Do Physical Exercise | Cook